rock929rocks.com 2019-06-01

# 

                                           Privacy Policy
Effective Date – April 19, 2017
Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy describes the types of information that
Beasley Broadcast Group, Inc. and its subsidiaries (collectively “Beasley,” “we”, “us”, or “our”)
collects from and about you when you visit or use our websites, web properties, interactive
features, iRadioNow, mobile apps, widgets, blogs, text message promotions, or any other website
or online service that includes an authorized link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the
“Platforms”), whether accessed via computer, mobile device, or other technology.
This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is made part of the website Terms of Service
(“TOS”). By visiting and using our Platforms, you agree to the collection, use, and disclosure of
your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not, please do not use
our Platforms.
1. INFORMATION WE COLLECT
•       Information You Provide
Beasley collects personal information from you on the Platforms when you choose to provide it
to us. This may include when you register on the Platforms, request information from us, submit
comments or participate in a promotion, survey or other feature of the Platforms, or otherwise
communicate or interact with us. The personal information we collect may include, but may not
be limited to, your name, email address, telephone number, address, gender, birth date, or other
profile-related information, and, if you make a purchase from us, a credit or debit card number or
other financial information.
•       Information Automatically Collected
We may use a variety of technologies such as cookies, pixel tags, web beacons, web server logs,
and other similar technologies to collect certain non-personal information about visitors to, and
users of, the Platforms and interactions with our emails and advertisements, and to allow Beasley
to keep track of analytics and certain statistical information.
For example, we may automatically collect information from your computer or other device used
to access the Platforms, including your Internet protocol address (“IP Address”) or other unique
device identifiers for mobile devices (“UDID”), browser type, device type, operating system, or
geolocation information, phone model, phone operating system, and the domain name from
which you accessed the Platform. We also may collect information about your use of the
Platforms, including the date and time you visit the Platforms, the areas or pages of the Platforms
that you visit, the amount of time you spend viewing or using the Platforms, the number of times
you return to the Platforms, other click-stream or site usage data, emails that you open, forward
or click-through to our Platforms, information about the website you were visiting before you
came to the Platforms and after you leave the Platforms, and your use of features or applications
on the Platforms.

Information You Provide Through Social Media. You may also be given the option to link to or
access your social media account(s) through the Platforms. When you do, we may automatically
receive certain information from you based upon your privacy settings on those social media
sites. This may include, but may not be limited to, your name, user name, demographic
information, updated address or contact information, location, interests, and publicly-observed
data, such as from social media and online activity.
Third Party Service Providers. We may use third party service providers to support our
Platforms. Some of these service providers may use technology such as cookies, web beacons,
pixel tags, log files, or Flash cookies to receive, collect, and store information.
Third Party Analytic Technologies. We may use third parties’ analytics and tracking tools to
better understand who is using the Platforms, how people are using the Platforms, how to
improve the effectiveness of the Platforms and related content, and to help us or those third
parties serve more targeted advertising to you across the Internet. These tools may use
technology such as cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, log files, Flash cookies, or other
technologies to collect and store non-personal information. They may also combine information
they collect from your interaction with the Platforms with information they collect from other
sources. We do not have access to, or control over, these third parties’ use of cookies or other
tracking technologies.
•       Information Collected From Other Sources; Combination of Information
We may acquire information from other trusted sources to update or supplement the information
that you provide or that we collect automatically (such as information to validate or update your
address or other demographic information). We may use this information to help us maintain the
accuracy of the information we collect, to target our communications so that we can inform you
of products and services or other offers that may be of interest to you, and for internal business
analysis or other business purposes.
We may combine the information we receive from or about you, including information you
provide to us and information we automatically collect through our Platforms, as well as
information collected offline, information across other computers or devices that you may use,
and information collected from other third party sources.
2. INFORMATION USE
We may use the information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes:
    •   To respond to your inquiries, fulfill orders, and contact and communicate with you when
        necessary;
    •   To enhance your online experience, including as a way to help identify you, your
        shopping preferences, and song history, and as a way to welcome you to the Platforms;
    •   To review the usage and operations of our Platforms, develop new products or services
        and conduce analysis to enhance or improve our content, products, and services;

    •   To provide you with customized content, targeted offers, and advertising on our
        Platforms, via email, text message or push notification, or across other websites, mobile
        applications, social media or online services;
    •   To provide you with access to certain areas and features of the Platforms such as your
        favorite stations, your musical preferences, songs you have listened to, shared playlists
        and your interaction with other users;
    •   To contact you with information, newsletters and promotional materials from Beasley or
        on behalf of our partners and affiliates;
    •   To use your data in an aggregated non-specific format for analytical and demographic
        purposes;
    •   To address problems with the Platforms or our business, and to protect the security or
        integrity of the Platforms and our business;
    •   To use and disclose your credit/debit card information only to process payments and
        prevent fraud;
    •   For other purposes disclosed at the time you provide your information or otherwise with
        your consent.
Additionally, if you use the Platforms to connect with third party services you authorize us to use
information from and about you, on your behalf, to interact with these third party services based
on your requests.
3. SHARING OF INFORMATION
Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, we will not disclose, sell, or rent any of your personal
information to any third parties without your specific consent. We may share the information we
collect from and about you in the following ways:
    •   Beasley Affiliates: We may share your information with Beasley affiliates and
        subsidiaries for business, operational, promotional and marketing purposes.
    •   Service Providers: We may share your information with third party service providers
        that provide business, professional or technical support functions for us, help us operate
        our business and the Platforms, or administer activities on our behalf.
    •   Co-Branded Relationships: Certain areas of our Platforms may be provided to you in
        association with third parties, such as advertisers that provide products and services or
        rewards programs. We may share information with these third parties if you participate
        in a co-branded, co-sponsored, or jointly presented promotion, contest, survey, voting
        feature, or service.
    •   Other Third Parties: We may share your information with our select partners, affiliates,
        and other third parties that we believe may have offers of interest to you.
    •   Legal Matters; Safety: We may access and disclose your information to respond to
        subpoenas, judicial processes, or government requests and investigations, or in
        connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law,
        or otherwise as required by law. We may disclose your information to protect the security
        of our Platforms, servers, network systems, and databases. We also may disclose your

        information as necessary, if we believe that there has been a violation of our TOS, any
        other legal document or contract related to our Services, or the rights of any third party.
    •   Sale or Transfer of Business or Assets: We may sell or purchase assets during the
        normal course of our business. In connection with any proposed or actual purchase, sale,
        lease, merger, assignment, re-organization or financing of all or any portion of Beasley,
        our Platforms, stations, or any of the business, assets or shares of our company(s) and
        affiliates, information we have collected about you may be transferred to such entity. In
        addition, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, such
        information may be considered an asset of ours and may be sold or transferred to third
        parties. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to try to
        require that the transferee use personal information provided through the Platform in a
        manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.
    •   Aggregate or Anonymous Non-Personal Information. We may also share aggregate or
        anonymous non-personal information with third parties for their marketing or analytics
        uses
    •   Other: We also may share your information as disclosed to you at the time of collection.
4. YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
If you are a California resident and have an established business relationship with Beasley, you
may request information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties or affiliated
companies for their direct marketing purposes. To make such request, please send your written
request following the instructions below. We will not accept requests via the telephone or
facsimile.
    •   For all requests, include your full name, street address, city, state and zip code, and the
        name of the Beasley Platform to which you are requesting the information.
    •   In your email request, you must state “Your California Privacy Rights” in the subject line
        and send your email to: privacy@bbgi.com.
    •   In your postal request, you must send a letter or post card to:
        Beasley Broadcast Group, Inc.
        3033 Riviera Drive, Suite 200
        Naples, FL 34103
        Attention: Your California Privacy Rights c/o Privacy Coordinator
Beasley is not responsible for responding to notices that are not properly labeled, not sent
properly, or do not have complete information. Non-affiliated third parties are independent
from Beasley and if you wish to receive information about your disclosure choices or stop
communications from such third parties after we have shared your personal information with
them, you will need to contact those non-affiliated third parties directly.

5. YOUR CHOICES AND OPT-OUT
Cookies, Tracking Options and California Do Not Track Disclosures
Certain parts of our Platforms require cookies. You are free to set your browser or operating
system settings to limit certain tracking or to decline cookies, but by doing so, you may not be
able to use certain features on the Platforms or take full advantage of all of our offerings. Please
refer to your Web browser’s or operating system’s website or “Help” section for more
information on how to delete and/or disable your browser or operating system from receiving
cookies or controlling your tracking preferences.
Our system may not respond to Do Not Track requests or headers from some or all browsers. We
may use cookies or other technologies to deliver more relevant advertising and to link data
collected across other computers or devices that you may use. To understand your choices for
receiving more relevant advertising or to manage your settings, please review the information
below:
    •   To learn more about the use of cookies or other technologies to deliver more relevant
        advertising and to know your choices with respect to collection and use of the data by
        these third party tools, you may visit: http://www.aboutads.info/choices/.
    •   If you wish to prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics, Google has
        developed the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on available here.
    •   Our mobile applications make use of third party services to collect anonymous mobile
        data in order to serve more relevant advertisements and content. If you wish to
        understand more about the data collected, or to opt-out, please visit
        http://revealmobile.com/privacy/.
    •   On your mobile device, you may also adjust your privacy and advertising settings to
        control whether you want to receive more relevant advertising.
Advertising Options Icon
For advertising that is part of a Network Advertising service, you should see a small symbol
(also called an icon) attached to a banner ad or other targeted advertising on certain Platforms
that can be clicked open for information about why and how you are receiving a particular ad.
For more information see www.aboutads.info.
Unsubscribing from Email Communications by Us:
We provide you with the opportunity to update your information or opt-out of having their
information used for purposes not directly related to placement, processing, fulfillment, or
delivery of a product order or servicing of your product. To opt-out of marketing
communications, you may:
    •   Send us an e-mail at privacy@bbgi.com; or

    •    Unsubscribe from our email communications at any time by unsubscribing or following
         the instructions contained within the email.
If you receive marketing communications from one or more Beasley affiliates, you must opt-out
individually from each of the affiliates from which you are receiving brand-specific marketing
communications.
Access and Updates to Your Information
If you wish to correct or update any of your personal information collected online through the
Platforms, you may email us at privacy@bbgi.com.
Please be aware that we do not control certain privacy settings and preferences maintained by
social media partners like Facebook and Twitter. If you wish to make changes to those settings
and preferences, you may do so by visiting the settings page of the appropriate social media site.
6. OTHER WEBSITES OR SERVICES
The Platforms may have links to third-party websites, apps, or services, which may have privacy
policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the practices of such third parties.
Any personal information submitted directly to an independent payment transaction provider for
purchase of goods, services and events on our Platforms is governed by the payment provider’s
terms of service and privacy policy. Visitors should consult all third party website privacy
policies as Beasley has no control or responsibility over information that is submitted to, or
collected by these third parties.
7. NOTE FOR PARENTS
Protecting children’s privacy is important to us. We do not direct the Platforms to, nor do we
knowingly collect any personal information from, children under the age of 13. If we learn that a
child under the age of 13 has provided personal information to us online, we will use reasonable
efforts to remove such information from our files, unless retaining such information is required
by statute, rule or regulation. For example, we are required by the Federal Communications
Commission to retain any correspondence received from a listener related to our programming
and operations in a public inspection file, and that would include correspondence from a child.
8. SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION.
Although we take appropriate and reasonable measures to help protect against the loss, misuse,
unauthorized disclosure, or alteration of your information, we cannot guarantee the security of
any information you transmit to us. If we collect sensitive personal information such as credit
card data, we will do so via a secured transmission standard or protocol, or engage a third party
to do so. Despite our best efforts, no security measures are impenetrable, and transmissions or
transactions over the Internet are not 100% secure or error free. You use the Platforms and
provide us with your information at your own risk.

9. DATA STORAGE AND TRANSFER
Your personal information may be stored and processed on servers in the United States and is
subject to the laws of the United States. The servers and databases in which information may be
stored may be located outside the country from which you accessed the Platforms and in a
country where the data protection and other laws may differ from your country of residence.
Your personal information may be disclosed in response to inquiries or requests from
government authorities or to respond to judicial process in the countries in which we operate.
Our operations are conducted, in whole or in part, in the United States. Regardless of where you
live, you consent to have your personal data transferred, processed and stored in the United
States, and allow us to collect and use your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
10. REVISIONS TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.
We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add or remove information on the
Platforms and/or this Privacy Policy, at any time without prior notice to you. Any changes will
be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy on the Platforms and we
encourage you to check back from time to time. If we change the Privacy Policy in a material
way, we will provide appropriate notice to you.
11. HOW TO CONTACT US.
If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, the practices of the Platforms, or
your experiences with the Platforms, please contact us at privacy@bbgi.com, or by mail to:
Beasley Broadcast Group, Inc.
3033 Riviera Drive, Suite 200
Naples, FL 34103
Attention: Privacy Coordinator
Copyright ©2009-2017 Beasley Broadcast Group, Inc.
